Guide to the Ronald Shiffman collection on the Pratt Center for Community Development 2013.023
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 11: General Correspondence
  - Internal Pratt Memos -- Inter-Office, 1990-1993 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Letters of Support for Other Organizations, 1991-1994 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Lower Density Rezoning Letter to Department of City Planning, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Marcy Benstock, Director, Clean Air Campaign Westwall, 1987 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Media/Technology -- PICCED Server and Data Storage Proposal, 1994-1999 (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Memorandum of Understanding Between Pratt Institute and PICCED, 2003-2004 (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - Memos re: Procedures, 1986-1987 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Middle States Assoication of Colleges and Schools Accredidation Visit -- General Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 106, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Letters, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Letters and Memos, 1994-2001 (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Letters and Memos, 1994-2001 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - News Clippings and Ford Foundation Correspondence, 1981-1989 (Box 107, Folder 2-3)
  - PCEDI Pratt Community Economic Development Internship Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - PICCED Bibliography, 1992-1999 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - PICCED Economic Development Strategy, Undated (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - PICCED Funding, 1974-1976 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - PICCED Grants and Fundraising, 1984-2000 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - PICCED Internal Memos, 1984-1988 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - PICCED Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - PICCED Related Articles, 1996-2003 (Box 110, Folder 6-8)
  - PICCED/PAC Trustee Briefing Paper, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Policy Committee and Staff Meetings, 1992-1995 (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Pratt Center Gallery, 1987 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Pratt Center Legal Issues, 1990-1993 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Raymond Rodriguez, 1986 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Recommendations for Ron Shiffman to College of Fellows of the American Institute of Certified Planners, 2001 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Ron and Yvette Shiffman Telegram to Andrew Cuomo, 1996 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Ron Correspondence, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Ron Correspondence, 1993-2000 (Box 107, Folder 17-18)
  - Ron Shiffman Correspondence with Yale Architectural Journal, Perspecta 31, 1996 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Ron-Staff Correspondence and PICCED Staff, 1989-1993 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Ron's Referrals, 1996-1997 (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Rudy Bryant Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - Seabrook, Luther, 1986 (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - Sean Robin Letter to Ron Shiffman -- Indiginous Planning Magazine, 2003 (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - Strategic Planning Steering Committee, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - Thank You Notes, 2001-2003 (Box 108, Folder 17)
  - The Hill -- Letters to Ron, 1992-1998 (Box 108, Folder 18)
  - Various Correspondence Outgoing, 1984-1987 (Box 108, Folder 19)
  - Visitors to the Center, 1991-1995 (Box 108, Folder 20)